this is Charlie Brown
the first brownie
format
skate wheel
I made a stuffing
called
original pink
a big brownie
stuffed
um this experience that I would like people to
receive
Charlie Brown
but today I received a message
left me very worried
the store arrived a little crumpled and so did the brownies
that's not an edible skateboard wheel
I ordered fifteen Charlie brownies
seven came dented
I bought the brownies a week ago
but I just saw that the mail sent to another city
experience I had here was not the desired one
is expensive
oh oh man
product
guy you are delivering here
and we are here with product
gotta pull up that rule brother bro
urgent
improve the online experience
I already spoke to Mateus earlier today
it's because we didn't have to fall with the paid traffic
if the box has no way
or us for operation
not to improve the end customer experience
because hand
there's how we get marketing across one way
people send me that the product is coming
all dented
is on
I'm going to take those three complaints I had
I'll go figure out a way to give them back
in a box
legal
it's connected to pass the bubble wrap around and zero
bro can pull
then you want me to get their address and send it to you
just take the order number
for us not to leave a bad experience
is on
I think it will be positive for us to reverse this
we can apologize there in a nice way
the first to receive an official box
already gives people a cooler experience brother
so it's us brother
I'll run with the ideas here too
show worth PC
we are with brother
bye that's the responsibility i have with you
that consumes my brand
show where we are going wrong
and have a commitment
to improve
is on
from now on
Charlie Brown and Junior
to arrive with the best possible experience
at the door of your house
tamo together valeu
passes over
don't keep marking the stutterers
sticks up in rhyme measure